OKAY, GREAT. BYE.
HEY. SO, GUESS
WHO'S COMING TO
THANKSGIVING DINNER?
SIDNEY POITIER.
( laughing )
I MISS RACHEL.
NO, MY PARENTS.
OH, THAT'S GREAT.
THEY HAVEN'T SEEN
THE PLACE SINCE
I MOVED IN.
YEAH, AND YOU KNOW
IF YOU COULD NOT
MENTION TO THEM
THAT WE LIVE TOGETHER,
THAT WOULD BE GREAT.
I WAS THINKING
WE'D EAT AROUND 4:00.
WHY CAN'T I TELL THEM
THAT WE LIVE TOGETHER?
BECAUSE THEY DON'T KNOW
WE'RE DATING.
DO YOU THINK
WE SHOULD EAT
IN THE KITCHEN?
WHY HAVEN'T YOU TOLD THEM?
UM, WELL, I WAS GOING TO,
I WAS REALLY WAS
BUT, UM, THEN, SOMEWHERE,
JUST OUT OF NOWHERE, I DIDN'T.
WHY HAVEN'T
YOU TOLD THEM?
WOULDN'T THEY
BE HAPPY?
SO DINNER IN THE KITCHEN
AROUND 4:00.
I'LL SEE YOU THEN.
WHY WOULDN'T THEY BE HAPPY?
WELL, UH, BECAUSE...
MAINLY, UH...
THEY DON'T LIKE YOU.
I'M SORRY.
WHAT? WHAT? WHY?
MAYBE BECAUSE YOU USED
TO BE ALOOF, OR THAT YOU'RE
REALLY SARCASTIC,
OR THAT, YOU KNOW
YOU JOKE AROUND ALL THE TIME
OR THAT YOU TAKE OFF
YOUR CLOTHES
AND YOU THROW THEM ON THE COUCH.
IS THIS WHY THEY DON'T LIKE ME
OR WHY YOU DON'T LIKE ME?
LOOK, I KNOW THAT I
SHOULD HAVE TOLD THEM.
I KNOW I SHOULDN'T CARE
WHAT THEY THINK. I'M SORRY.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
IT'LL BE OKAY, IT'LL BE OKAY
BECAUSE WHEN THEY COME OVER,
I WILL BE ALL CHARMING.
I WILL MAKE THEM
FALL IN LOVE WITH ME
AND THEN WE'LL TELL THEM.
YOU REALLY THINK THAT'LL WORK?
HEY, I CAN BE
PRETTY CHARMING, BABE.
WON YOU OVER, DIDN'T I?
I DON'T THINK YOU'LL EVER GET
MY PARENTS THAT DRUNK.
♪ SO NO ONE TOLD YOU
LIFE WAS GONNA BE THIS WAY ♪
♪ YOUR JOB'S A JOKE,
YOU'RE BROKE ♪
♪ YOUR LOVE LIFE'S D.O.A. ♪
♪ IT'S LIKE YOU'RE ALWAYS
STUCK IN SECOND GEAR ♪
♪ WHEN IT HASN'T BEEN
YOUR DAY, YOUR WEEK ♪
♪ YOUR MONTH,
OR EVEN YOUR YEAR ♪
♪ BUT I'LL BE THERE FOR YOU ♪
♪ 'CAUSE YOU'RE THERE
FOR ME, TOO. ♪
HEY. OH, GOOD.
ROSS,
YOUR PARENTS
LIKE ME, RIGHT?
YES, OF COURSE
THEY LIKE YOU.
WELL, MONICA JUST TOLD ME
THAT THEY DON'T.
YEAH, THEY DON'T LIKE YOU.
DO YOU KNOW WHY?
I DON'T KNOW. MAYBE IT'S 'CAUSE
YOU'RE REALLY SARCASTIC
OR, I DON'T KNOW,
MAYBE IT'S 'CAUSE...
WELL, IF PEOPLE DON'T KNOW
THEY SHOULDN'T
JUST GUESS.
THIS IS GREAT.
ANOTHER THANKSGIVING
WITH NOTHING
TO GIVE THANKS FOR.
MAYBE I GIVE THANKS FOR
YOU SHUTTING UP, HUH?
MAYBE I GIVE THANKS
BY TAKING MY PLAYSTATION
OVER TO MY NEW APARTMENT.
WELL, MAYBE I LOVE YOU.
( sarcastic mimicking )
HI.
HEY, GUYS.
NO, I DON'T WANT TO
PLAY VIDEO GAMES, JOE.
ARE YOU GUYS GOING TO CHANDLER'S
FOR THANKSGIVING?
YEAH, YEAH, WHY?
WHAT'S UP?
WELL, ME AND MY DANCER FRIENDS
ARE THINKING
OF DOING THANKSGIVING UPTOWN.
I THOUGHT YOU GUYS
MIGHT LIKE TO COME.
FOR REAL?
YOU SHOULD GO TO CHANDLER'S
BECAUSE NONE OF US
KNOWS HOW TO COOK.
WE'LL PROBABLY JUST END UP
DRINKING ALL DAY.
YEAH.
WE GO TO YOURS, YEAH.
YEAH. SEE, WE HAVE TO
STOP ACROSS THE HALL
'CAUSE IT'S MY SISTER,
BUT YOU KNOW, ACTUALLY
GROWING UP
WITH A SISTER WAS NICE
BECAUSE IT REALLY HELPED ME
UNDERSTAND WOMEN.
YOU SHOULD TELL
YOUR FRIENDS THAT.
OKAY.
HOW YOU GOT THREE WOMEN
TO MARRY YOU, I'LL NEVER KNOW.
HEY.
HEY, PHEEBS, CHECK IT OUT.
YEAH.
FOR MY DESSERT
I HAVE CHOSEN TO MAKE
A TRADITIONAL ENGLISH TRIFLE.
WOW, THAT SOUNDS GREAT.
AND WHAT ARE YOU MAKING, MONICA,
YOU KNOW
IN CASE RACHEL'S DESSERT
IS SO GOOD THAT I EAT ALL OF IT.
THERE'S NONE LEFT
FOR ANYBODY ELSE.
NOTHING.
NOTHING?
YEAH, SWEETIE,
I TRUST YOU.
SO IF I MESS THIS UP, THERE'S
NOTHING ELSE FOR DESSERT?
YOU'RE NOT GOING TO MESS IT UP.
WOW, MONICA, I LOVE THAT.
YOU REALLY HAVE FAITH IN ME.
THANK YOU.
TECHNICAL QUESTION.
HOW DO YOU KNOW
WHEN THE BUTTER IS DONE?
WELL, IT'S DONE ABOUT
TWO MINUTES BEFORE
IT LOOKS THAT.
HEY.
OH, THE FOOD
SMELLS GREAT, MON.
YEAH, AND THE PLACE
LOOKS SO NICE.
HEY, HAPPY THANKSGIVING,
EVERYBODY.
HAPPY THANKSGIVING.
All:
WELL, THIS HAS BEEN GREAT.
SEE YA.
WHOA, WHOA, WHOA.
WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
OH, WE DID SAY
WE'D STOP BY THIS
LITTLE THING JOEY'S
ROOMMATE IS HAVING.
OH, JANINE, THE REALLY
HOT DANCER GIRL?
SOME WOULD SAY
SHE'S ATTRACTIVE, YES.
AND WHO ELSE
IS GOING TO BE THERE?
SOME OF HER FRIENDS.
HER DANCER FRIENDS?
YES, ALL RIGHT?
ALL OF HER HOT DANCER FRIENDS
ARE GOING TO BE THERE
AND THEY'LL BE DRINKING
AND DANCING
AND WE REALLY WANT TO GO.
DUDE, WE WERE GOOD.
YOU'RE NOT GOING
TO GO ANYWHERE.
YOU SAID YOU WERE GOING
TO EAT HERE AND YOU'RE
GOING TO EAT HERE.
AND LEAVING US
TO GO SEE HOT DANCER GIRLS
IS NOT VERY THANKSGIVING-Y.
OH, BUT IT IS.
IT'S JUST LIKE
THE FIRST THANKSGIVING
WHEN THE INDIANS
AND THE PILGRIMS
SAT DOWN TO DINNER.
YEAH, YEAH, AND THEN
THE INDIANS TAUGHT
THE PILGRIMS
WHAT IT MEANT TO BE HOT
IN THE NEW WORLD.
HI.
HELLO, EVERYBODY.
HI, DAD. MOM.
LOOK... LOOK WHO IT IS.
IT'S CHANDLER.
OH, YES, OF COURSE.
HELLO, CHANDLER.
MR. AND MRS. GELLER,
YOU LOOK WONDERFUL.
IT IS GREAT TO
HAVE YOU HERE.
LET US TAKE
OFF YOUR COATS.
WHOA, SNOWING OUT THERE?
NO.
MONICA, ALL THIS FOOD
LOOKS WONDERFUL.
YOU SHOULD THINK
ABOUT DOING THIS
FOR A LIVING.
OKAY. I HAVE DANDRUFF.
THERE'S NO NEED
TO LAUGH AND POINT.
DAD, CHANDLER WAS JUST LAUGHING
AT YOUR JOKE.
MY JOKE WASN'T FUNNY.
RACH, RACH...
YEAH.
I JUST REMEMBERED.
I HAD A DREAM ABOUT
MR. GELLER LAST NIGHT.
REALLY?
YEAH.
I DREAMT THAT HE
SAVED ME FROM A
BURNING BUILDING
AND HE WAS SO BRAVE
AND SO STRONG
AND IT'S MAKING ME
LOOK AT HIM
TOTALLY DIFFERENTLY.
YOU KNOW?
I MEAN, HE USED TO
BE JUST, YOU KNOW
JACK GELLER, MONICA
AND ROSS'S DAD
AND NOW HE'S
JACK GELLER,
DREAM HUNK.
Rachel:
I DON'T KNOW.
YOU KNOW, TO ME,
HE'LL ALWAYS BE
JACK GELLER--
WALKS IN WHILE
YOU'RE CHANGING.
YOU KNOW, DAD,
CHANDLER IS ONE
OF ROSS'S VERY
BEST FRIENDS.
YOU KNOW,
ROSS SURE IS A GREAT GUY.
YOU KNOW, I'VE ALWAYS FELT
THAT HOW A YOUNG MAN TURNS OUT
IS A REFLECTION ON HIS FATHER.
I ALWAYS THOUGHT THAT, TOO.
TELL ME,
WHAT DOES YOUR FATHER DO?
HE'S A HEADLINER OF A...
GAY BURLESQUE SHOW.
RACH, YOU'RE KILLING US HERE.
WILL YOU SERVE
THE DESSERT ALREADY?
THERE'S DRUNKEN
DANCERS AWAITING.
WELL, LOOK AT IT.
ISN'T IT BEAUTIFUL?
YEAH, YEAH,
WHAT IS IT?
IT'S A TRIFLE
AND IT'S GOT ALL
OF THESE LAYERS.
FIRST, THERE'S A LAYER
OF LADYFINGERS
THEN A LAYER OF JAM
THEN CUSTARD,
WHICH I MADE FROM SCRATCH.
THEN RASPBERRIES
MORE LADYFINGERS
THEN BEEF SAUTEED
WITH PEAS AND ONIONS
AND THEN A LITTLE
BIT MORE CUSTARD,
AND THEN BANANAS
AND THEN I JUST PUT
SOME WHIPPED CREAM ON TOP.
WHAT WAS THE ONE
RIGHT BEFORE BANANAS?
THE BEEF? YEAH, THAT
WAS WEIRD TO ME, TOO,
BUT, THEN, YOU KNOW
I THOUGHT, WELL,
THERE'S MINCEMEAT PIE.
I MEAN, THAT'S AN
ENGLISH DESSERT.
THESE PEOPLE JUST PUT
VERY STRANGE THINGS
IN THEIR FOOD, YOU KNOW?
OH, BY THE WAY, CAN I BORROW
SOME RUM FROM YOUR PLACE?
YEAH, SURE, YEAH.
AND WHILE I'M GONE,
DON'T YOU BOYS SNEAK A TASTE.
RIGHT.
OKAY.
BEEF IN A DESSERT?
THERE... NO, NO, NO.
THERE IS NO WAY.
I KNOW, AND ONLY
ONE LAYER OF JAM?
WHAT IS UP WITH THAT?
OH, MY GOD.
THE PAGES ARE STUCK TOGETHER.
CHANDLER!
OH, MY GOD.
SHE... SHE MADE HALF
AN ENGLISH TRIFLE AND...
HALF A SHEPHERD'S PIE.
OH, MAN.
NOW SHE'S GOING
TO START ALL OVER.
WE'RE NEVER GOING
TO GET TO INTRODUCE
THE HOT GIRLS
TO THE NEW WORLD.
NO, NO, WE WILL.
WE JUST WON'T TELL HER
SHE MESSED UP.
JUST LET HER SERVE
THE BEEF CUSTARD THING?
YEAH.
IT WILL BE LIKE A FUNNY
THANKSGIVING STORY.
VOMITING STORIES
ARE FUNNY, I GUESS.
JOEY, GOD, YOUR APARTMENT
IS, LIKE, A HUNDRED DEGREES.
DID IT MAKE YOU WANT
TO WALK AROUND IN
YOUR UNDERWEAR?
NO.
STILL NOT HOT ENOUGH.
YEAH.
RACHEL.
OKAY. LOOK AT HIM.
LOOK AT THOSE
STRONG HANDS.
OH, WHAT I WOULDN'T
GIVE TO BE THAT CAN
OF CONDENSED MILK.
MOM, CHANDLER
WAS JUST SAYING
HOW BEAUTIFUL
YOUR SWEATER IS.
OH, THANK YOU, CHANDLER.
I JUST BOUGHT IT.
OH, YES. WELL,
IT'S VERY BEAUTIFUL.
IT'S CREAM-COLORED
AND TIGHT, AND...
I DON'T MEAN TIGHT.
IT'S NOT TOO TIGHT.
NOT THAT I WAS LOOKING AT...
WHAT'S THE MATTER
WITH HIM?
I THINK HE'S STONED AGAIN.
WHAT?
DUDE, I NEED TO TALK TO YOU
A SEC.
OKAY.
I THINK I MIGHT KNOW WHY
MY PARENTS DON'T LIKE YOU.
YOU DO? WHY?
OKAY, REMEMBER--
WE WERE YOUNG...
SPRING BREAK,
SOPHOMORE YEAR.
I GOT HIGH
IN MY BEDROOM
AND MY PARENTS WALKED IN
AND SMELLED IT
AND SO I TOLD THEM
THAT YOU HAD GOTTEN STONED
AND JUMPED OUT THE WINDOW.
WHAT?
WHY DID YOU DO THAT?
I DON'T KNOW.
YOURS WAS THE FIRST NAME
THAT POPPED INTO MY HEAD.
I'M SORRY.
I DIDN'T THINK IT WOULD MATTER.
HOW COULD IT NOT MATTER?
WELL, HOW WAS I
SUPPOSED TO KNOW
WE'D END UP BEING
FRIENDS AFTER COLLEGE
LET ALONE YOU'D BE
LIVING WITH MY SISTER?
WHAT ABOUT ALL THAT
"FRIENDS FOREVER" STUFF?
I DON'T KNOW.
I WAS ALL HIGH.
MOM AND DAD JUST SENT ME
IN HERE TO FIND OUT
IF YOU WERE TRYING
TO GET ROSS STONED.
YOUR PARENTS CAUGHT ROSS
SMOKING POT IN COLLEGE
AND HE BLAMED IT ON ME.
ROSS, I CAN'T BELIEVE
YOU'D DO THAT.
THE REASON WE HAVEN'T
TOLD THEM WE'RE TOGETHER
IS BECAUSE THEY HATE ME.
OKAY? SO, WILL
YOU FIX THIS?
OKAY. OKAY.
I'LL TELL THEM
IT WASN'T CHANDLER WHO GOT HIGH.
NOW, WHO SHOULD I SAY IT WAS?
YOU!
IT'S NOT LIKE
IT WAS A BIG DEAL.
YOU DON'T STILL
DO IT OR ANYTHING.
ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT.
NOW, WHO SHOULD I SAY
"TRICKED" ME INTO DOING IT?
DAD.
DAD, PLEASE DON'T
PICK YOUR TEETH OUT HERE.
ALL RIGHT, AND IF YOU'RE
GOING TO PUT YOUR FEET UP...
MONICA, LEAVE HIM ALONE!
WILL YOU HURRY UP!
DID YOU NOT
HEAR ME BEFORE
WHEN I TOLD YOU THAT
ALL OF JANINE'S FRIENDS
ARE DANCERS, HUH?
AND THAT THEY'RE GOING
TO BE DRINKING A LOT?
NO, I DID, BUT TELL ME AGAIN
'CAUSE IT'S SO ROMANTIC.
YOU'RE WHIPPING SO SLOW.
CAN'T YOU DO IT ANY FASTER?
JOEY, COME ON.
I DON'T WANT TO MAKE
ANY MISTAKES, ALL RIGHT?
THIS IS THE ONLY DESSERT
AND IF I SCREW IT UP
EVERYBODY'S GOING
TO BE, LIKE
"OH, REMEMBER
THAT THANKSGIVING
WHEN RACHEL SCREWED
UP THE TRIFLE?"
OKAY?
SO WHY DON'T YOU JUST
LET ME WORRY ABOUT
MAKING THE TRIFLE
AND YOU JUST WORRY
ABOUT EATING IT,
ALL RIGHT?
OH, I AM.
ROSS, IF YOU
DON'T TELL THEM,
THEN I WILL.
OKAY, FINE.
ROSS, CAN I TALK
TO YOU FOR A SECOND?
OH, UH, CAN'T IT
WAIT A SECOND, JOEY?
I HAVE TO TELL MY
PARENTS SOMETHING.
NO, IT CAN'T?
OKAY.
OKAY, LOOK, I THINK
WE HAVE TO TELL RACHEL
SHE MESSED UP HER DESSERT.
WHAT? WHAT IS
WITH EVERYBODY?
IT'S THANKSGIVING,
NOT TRUTH DAY.
LOOK, WHEN EVERYONE EATS
THAT BANANA MEAT THING
THEY'RE ALL GOING
TO MAKE FUN OF HER.
DO YOU WANT THAT?
OKAY, OKAY, WE'LL
JUST GET EVERYONE
TO ACT LIKE
THEY LIKE IT.
THAT WAY, NO ONE
MAKES FUN OF HER
AND WE STILL GET TO GO
TO SWEET POTATO PIE.
DUDE, THEY'RE NOT OBJECTS.
JUST KIDDING.
I'LL TALK TO THEM.
YOU DISTRACT HER.
HEY, RACH, CAN I TALK
TO YOU OUTSIDE FOR A SEC?
OKAY.
WHAT'S UP, ROSS?
SO, UM...
THANKSGIVING.
THE HOLIDAY SEASON
IS UPON US, HMM?
YEAH.
AND, UM, YOU
LOOK NICE TODAY.
OH, NO.
NO, ROSS. DON'T DO THIS.
WHAT?
I JUST... I DON'T THINK
US GETTING BACK TOGETHER
IS A GOOD IDEA.
HUH?
I THOUGHT THIS MIGHT
HAPPEN TODAY. ROSS...
I KNOW THE HOLIDAYS
CAN BE ROUGH, YOU KNOW?
AND IT'S PROBABLY REALLY HARD
FOR YOU TO BE ALONE RIGHT NOW.
YOU'RE ALONE.
NO, I-I LIVE
WITH PHOEBE.
I MEAN, YOU'RE
ALONE ALONE.
YOU KNOW?
AND I JUST...
IT'S JUST NOT
THE TIME FOR US.
I'M SORRY.
OH, WELL. CAN'T BLAME
A GUY FOR TRYING.
SO...
( stutters )
OKAY...
AND, UH, IF ANYONE
NEEDS HELP
PRETENDING
TO LIKE IT
I LEARNED SOME THINGS
IN ACTING CLASS.
TRY RUBBING YOUR STOMACH.
OR, UH...
OR SAYING "MMM."
AND, UH, OOH, OHH-- SMILING.
OKAY.
I'M NOT GOING TO PAY FOR
THOSE ACTING CLASSES ANYMORE.
Joey:
RACHEL, THERE
YOU ARE.
COME ON. LET'S SERVE
THAT DESSERT ALREADY.
JOEY, YOU'RE GOING
TO HAVE TO STOP RUSHING ME.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
YOU DON'T GET ANY DESSERT.
REALLY?
NO, I'M JUST KIDDING.
I WOULD NEVER
DO THAT TO YOU.
OKAY, EVERYBODY,
IT'S TRIFLE TIME.
SO, NOW, RACH...
THIS IS A TRADITIONAL
ENGLISH TRIFLE, ISN'T IT?
IT SURE IS.
WOW. SO, THEN, DID YOU MAKE IT
WITH BEEF OR EGGPLANT?
BEEF.
I CAN'T HAVE ANY, YOU KNOW?
I DON'T EAT BEEF.
( all groaning and sighing )
ALL RIGHT, MONICA
I WANT YOU TO HAVE
THE FIRST TASTE.
REALLY?
OH, WAIT-WAIT!
YOU ONLY GOT WHIPPED CREAM
IN THERE.
YOU'VE GOT TO TAKE A BITE
WITH ALL
THE LAYERS.
OKAY.
OOPS, YOU DROPPED A PEA.
WELL?
MMM...
IT'S GOOD.
REALLY? HOW GOOD?
IT'S SO GOOD THAT I
FEEL REALLY SELFISH
BEING THE ONLY ONE
WHO'S EATING IT.
AND I THINK WE SHOULD
HAVE EVERYONE TASTE
HOW GOOD IT IS.
ESPECIALLY ROSS.
MM-HMM.
All:
MMM...
YEAH, THIS IS SO GOOD
THAT I'M GOING TO GO
ENJOY IT ON THE BALCONY.
SO I CAN ENJOY THE VIEW
WHILST I ENJOY MY DESSERT.
AND I'M GOING TO CALL
MY FRIEND, MARY
AND TELL HER HOW GOOD
THIS IS FROM MONICA'S ROOM.
I'LL HELP YOU DIAL.
AND I'M GOING TO GO
INTO THE BATHROOM
SO I CAN LOOK AT IT
IN THE MIRROR AS I EAT IT.
OKAY, NOW, WHAT WAS THAT
ALL ABOUT?
IS IT...
DOES IT NOT TASTE GOOD?
LET ME TRY THAT.
NO! NO!
ALL GONE.
SO GOOD.
MAYBE CHANDLER
HAS SOME LEFT.
IT TASTES LIKE FEET.
I LIKE IT.
ARE YOU KIDDING?
WHAT'S NOT TO LIKE?
CUSTARD? GOOD.
JAM? GOOD.
MEAT? GOOD!
SO A BIRD JUST GRABBED IT
AND THEN...
AND THEN TRIED
TO FLY AWAY WITH IT AND...
AND THEN JUST DROPPED IT
ON THE STREET?
YES, BUT IF IT'S
ANY CONSOLATION
BEFORE THE BIRD DROPPED IT,
HE SEEMED TO ENJOY IT.
RACHEL, COME HERE.
OKAY...
I WAS JUST STARTING
TO TAKE MY THANKSGIVING NAP
AND I HAD ANOTHER
DREAM ABOUT JACK.
UH, PHOEBE, DO I
WANT TO HEAR THIS?
I DON'T KNOW.
LET'S SEE.
SO... OKAY, I DREAMT
THAT WE WERE GOING
TO GET MARRIED
AND HE LEFT BECAUSE
HE HAD TO GO FIGHT A FIRE.
AND, UM, SO, OKAY,
I WENT TO A NIGHTCLUB
AND I SAW HIM MAKING OUT
WITH A GIRL.
OH, MY GOD.
HE DREAM-CHEATED ON YOU.
YEAH. BUT THEN
JACQUES COUSTEAU CAME
AND HE KICKED HIS ASS
FOR BETRAYING ME.
HE WAS SO COOL.
AND THEN, HE
TOOK ME DIVING
AND HE INTRODUCED ME
TO HIS PET SEA HORSE
WHO, BY THE WAY, WAS
TOTALLY COMING ON TO ME
AND PLEASE, THAT IS
NOT GOING TO HAPPEN.
BOY, I'M GLAD I WORE
THE BIG BELT TODAY.
WOW.
FIVE MINUTES AGO,
A LINE LIKE THAT
WOULD HAVE FLOORED ME.
NOW NOTHING.
WELL, NOT NOTHING.
I AM STILL A WOMAN.
ROSS...
LET'S GO.
OH, YEAH, ABOUT TELLING
MOM AND DAD
I WAS THINKING ABOUT
MAYBE WRITING A LETTER.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
THAT'S IT.
YOU'VE HAD YOUR CHANCE.
MOM, DAD, ROSS
SMOKED POT IN COLLEGE.
WHAT?
YOU ARE SUCH A TATTLETALE!
MOM, DAD...
YOU REMEMBER THAT...
THAT TIME YOU WALKED IN MY ROOM
AND SMELLED MARIJUANA?
YES.
WELL, I TOLD YOU IT WAS CHANDLER
WHO WAS SMOKING THE POT, BUT...
IT WAS ME.
I'M SORRY.
IT WAS YOU?
Monica:
AND DAD
YOU KNOW THAT MAILMAN
THAT YOU GOT FIRED?
HE DIDN'T STEAL YOUR PLAYBOYS.
ROSS DID.
OH...
YEAH, WELL, HURRICANE GLORIA
DIDN'T BREAK THE PORCH SWING.
MONICA DID!
ROSS HASN'T WORKED
AT THE MUSEUM FOR A YEAR!
MONICA AND CHANDLER
ARE LIVING TOGETHER!
ROSS MARRIED RACHEL IN VEGAS
AND GOT DIVORCED AGAIN!
I LOVE JACQUES COUSTEAU!
I WASN'T SUPPOSED
TO PUT BEEF IN THE TRIFLE!
I WANT TO GO!
THAT'S A LOT OF INFORMATION
TO GET IN 30 SECONDS.
ALL RIGHT
JOEY, IF YOU WANT
TO LEAVE, JUST LEAVE.
RACHEL, NO, YOU WEREN'T
SUPPOSED TO PUT BEEF
IN THE TRIFLE.
IT DID NOT TASTE GOOD.
PHOEBE, I'M SORRY, BUT I THINK
JACQUES COUSTEAU IS DEAD.
MONICA...
WHY YOU FELT
YOU HAD TO
HIDE THE FACT
THAT YOU ARE IN AN IMPORTANT
RELATIONSHIP IS BEYOND ME.
AND WE KIND OF FIGURED
ABOUT THE PORCH SWING.
ROSS...
DRUGS, DIVORCED... AGAIN.
WHAT HAPPENED, SON?
I... I, UH, I GOT TRICKED
INTO ALL THOSE THINGS.
CHANDLER, YOU'VE BEEN
ROSS'S BEST FRIEND
ALL THESE YEARS
STUCK BY HIM
DURING THE DRUG PROBLEMS.
AND NOW YOU'VE
TAKEN ON MONICA AS WELL.
WELL, I DON'T KNOW
WHAT TO SAY.
YOU'RE A WONDERFUL
HUMAN BEING.
THANK YOU.
NO!
AND MONICA AND ROSS
I DON'T KNOW WHAT I'M GOING
TO DO ABOUT THE TWO OF YOU.
I'LL TALK TO THEM.
YOU GUYS,
IT WAS BANANAS
CREAM AND BEEF.
I JUST CANNOT BELIEVE
THAT YOU ATE THAT
SO THAT I WOULDN'T FEEL BAD.
ACTUALLY, I
DIDN'T EAT MINE.
IT'S STILL IN
THE BATHROOM.
NO, IT ISN'T.
I ATE THAT.
AND WE LEFT OURS
IN MONICA'S BEDROOM.
NO. GOT IT
AND GOT YOURS, TOO.